{
  "1": {
    "answers": {
      "0": "Writing tests before the code is written",
      "1": "Writing tests after the code is written",
      "2": "Writing the tests and code side by side",
      "3": "Writing all of the test after the all of the code is written"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "0",
    "question": "What statement best describes test-driven development?"
  },
  "2": {
    "answers": {
      "0": "Small responsibility please?",
      "1": "Single responsibility principle",
      "2": "Simulataneous reaction probability",
      "3": "Single rows pass"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "1",
    "question": "What does SRP stand for?"
  },
  "3": {
    "answers": {
      "0": "Every file should be responsibile for one part of the program",
      "1": "Every class should be responsibile for one part of the program",
      "2": "Every line should be responsibile for one part of the program",
      "3": "Every variable should be responsibile for one part of the program"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "1",
    "question": "What is the single responsibility principle?"
  },
  "4": {
    "answers": {
      "0": "Out Of Date",
      "1": "Orthogonally Objective Design",
      "2": "Object Of Desire",
      "3": "Object Oriented Design"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "3",
    "question": "What does OOD stand for?"
  },
  "5": {
    "answers": {
      "0": "String.concat()",
      "1": "Array.splice()",
      "2": "window.fetch()",
      "3": "window.alert()"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "2",
    "question": "Which of the following JavaScript functions are asynchronous?"
  },
  "6": {
    "answers": {
      "0": "Program is executed line by line. Executions waits for functions to return a value before continuing",
      "1": "Program is executed line by line. Executions waits a default time for function to return a value before continuing",
      "2": "Program is executed line by line. Executions does not wait for functions to return a value before continuing",
      "3": "Program is executed line by line. Exection is stopped by errors"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "2",
    "question": "Which of the following best describes asynchronous behaviour?"
  },
  "7": {
    "answers": {
      "0": "Program is executed line by line. Executions waits for functions to return a value before continuing",
      "1": "Program is executed line by line. Executions waits a default time for function to return a value before continuing",
      "2": "Program is executed line by line. Executions does not wait for functions to return a value before continuing",
      "3": "Program is executed line by line. Exection is stopped by errors"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "1",
    "question": "Which of the following best describes synchronous behaviour?"
  },
  "8": {
    "answers": {
      "0": "Copy, Read, Understand, Destroy",
      "1": "Copy, Read, Update, Delete",
      "2": "Create, Read, Update, Delete",
      "3": "Create, Read, Update, Destroy"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "2",
    "question": "What does CRUD stand for?"
  },
  "9": {
    "answers": {
      "0": "Send",
      "1": "Post",
      "2": "Patch",
      "3": "Get"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "0",
    "question": "Which of the following is not a HTTP method?"
  },
  "10": {
    "answers": {
      "0": "JSON",
      "1": "XML",
      "2": "CSV",
      "3": "SQL"
    },
    "correctAnswer": "0",
    "question": "What is the most common format for data retrieved from a server by a client?"
  }
}
